coolspotters.com 2012-11-08

# Privacy Policy - Fanzter

_Last updated June 13, 2011_

[Fanzter Inc.](http://fanzter.com/ "Fanzter Inc. - A New Media Development Company") (the parent company of this service; hereafter "Fanzter") respects and appreciates your interest in the privacy of your personal information. As such, we take the policies and practices covered below very seriously. In order to fully understand how your information is used and shared, we recommend that you read this policy (“The Fanzter Privacy Policy”) in its entirety. 

_In order to use certain services of Fanzter, such as uploading images, adding comments, or asking questions to the service’s community, you must register. As part of the registration process, we may require your email address. Nobody under the age of 13 is permitted to register. By not registering, you understand that certain features and services may not be available to you._

### Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our Sites and Services.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to our Sites and Services.
  * You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

### The Information We Collect

  * We collect personal information for the purpose of offering a personalized, enjoyable experience. We do not collect information unless it is relevant to the primary purpose of our Site or Service.
  * We collect personal information that you provide directly to us. Any information entered by you on any Fanzter Site or Service will be stored by us.
  * We collect information about your usage of Fanzter Sites or Services. As such, we may include on any page various metrics/data that illustrate your activity on the site (such as uploads, feedback, added contacts, etc.)
  * Any personal information or content that you voluntarily disclose or upload to the site will become publicly available and, as such, can be collected and used by others.
  * We use cookies to store information so that your information will not have to be re-entered upon re-visiting the site. Cookies will also enable us to provide personalized content information, monitor our own marketing campaigns, and track your entries and submissions on our site.

### Other Sharing of Information

We neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone. We share your information only with the entities as described below:

  * Affiliates – Fanzter is affiliated with a variety of businesses. We will only share information that is necessary for the affiliate to complete a process (a transaction, for example). We require our affiliates to provide the same level of privacy protection that we do.
  * Agents – Fanzter employs other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and may need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Some examples of this include providing customer service, removing illicit or indecent content, analyzing data, or providing marketing assistance.
  * Promotions – We may send promotional offers to registered users on behalf of other businesses. Although we will not give them your address or phone number, you can cancel the receipt of these offers by emailing us at [legal@fanzter.com](mailto:legal@fanzter.com).
  * Business Transfers – In the case of Fanzter buying or selling assets, personal customer information will be considered a business asset and as such, we retain the right to transfer this information as part of any such transaction.
  * Corporate Responsibility – We retain the right to release personal information when it is reasonably believed that release is necessary to comply with the law. We may also do so in the case of enforcing our Terms of Service (or other agreements), or protecting the rights, property, or safety of Fanzter, the users of any Fanzter Sites or Services, our employees, or others.

### Security of Information/Password

We recommend you always keep your password private and secure. It is also recommended that, when using a shared computer, you completely log off from our site in order to prevent unauthorized access to your password. 

### Policy Toward Children

Our Sites and Services are not directed to people under the age of 13. If you become aware that your child has registered to use one of our Sites or Service without your consent, please contact us at [legal@fanzter.com](mailto:legal@fanzter.com). We do not knowingly collect personal information from people under the age of 13. If we become aware that a person under the age of 13 has provided us with personal information, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the person's account. 

### Modification of the Privacy Policy

  * Fanzter reserves the right, in its sole discretion, at any time to modify, discontinue or terminate its Services or Services, or modify this Privacy Policy without notice.
  * All modified terms and conditions will be effective after they are posted on the Sites and Services (unless a longer notice period is required by applicable law).
  * If any changes we make to this policy are not acceptable to you, your sole remedy is to cease using the Sites or Services, and if applicable, cancel your related account.
  * By continuing to access or use the Sites or Services after Fanzter makes any such revision, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.
